trait-tech.com 2013-04-08

# Privacy notice - TRAIT TECH - Wholesale CellPhone Cases - China Wholesale - Dropship From China

**TRAIT-TECH** respects your privacy and takes your online safety seriously. In order to provide you with the best products, efficient customer service, and timely updates, we record a variety of information from your visit to our site. To better protect your privacy, we provide the notice below explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

## Information Collection and Use

### 1\. Information Collection.

When you visit our website, we do not collect personally identifiable information, except you specifically and knowingly provide it. For instance, we do require registration for the newsletter. If you decide to register as the newsletter, or if you are requested the information from us, your certain information and details, including your name, country and e-mail address will be asked to offer. One goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. For example, we can use your personal information to:

  * Help make this Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.
  * Help you quickly find information, products, services and Order.
  * Help us create content on this Site that is most relevant to you.
  * Alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer.

**a) Registration and Ordering.** Before using certain parts of this Site or ordering products, you must complete an online registration form. During registration, you will be prompted to provide us with certain personal information, including but not limited to your name, shipping and billing address, phone number, email address. In addition, we may also ask you for your country of residence and/or your organization's country of operation, so that we can comply with applicable laws and regulations. These kinds of personal information are used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order and our site, and for internal marketing purposes. If we encounter a problem when processing your order, we may use the personal information you provide us with to contact you.

**b) Email Addresses.** Several locations of the Site permit you to enter your email address for purposes including but not limited to: to register for free promotional notices; to request us to notify you when we receive a new brand, or new product style; to sign up for our email newsletter. You always have a choice of receiving mailings, surveys or information about our products and services. Each e-mail you receive has an "Unsubscribe" option. As a registered member, you can also advise us which types of e-mail you wish to receive by updating your Notifications page.

### 2\. Information Use and Disclosure.

**a) Internal Use.** We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may internally use your personal information to improve our Site's content and layout, to improve our outreach and for our own marketing efforts (including marketing our services and products to you), and to determine general marketplace information about visitors to this Site.

**b) Communications with You:** We will use your personal information to communicate with you about our site, and your orders and deliveries. Also, we may send you a confirmation email when you register with us. Also, you may submit your email address for reasons such as to request us to notify you when we receive a new brand, new product style, or product; to sign up for our email newsletter and special offers.

**c) Shipping Order to you:** In order to deliver products to you, we must share some information to third parties (such as DHL/UPS/EMS) to ship products, to ensure delivery. In the example of shippers, we provide them some personally identifiable information such as your name, shipping address, email, and phone number.

**d) Required by Law:** We may be required to disclose such information in response to requests from law-enforcement officials conducting investigations, subpoenas, a court order, or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law. We also will release personal information where disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights, enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect ourselves or others. For example, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud or if someone uses or attempts to use our Site for illegal reasons or to commit fraud.

**e) We will not sell (or trade or rent) personally identifiable information to other companies as part of our regular course of business.** However, it is possible that we might acquire or merge with or be acquired by another company or that we might dispose of some or all of our assets. If that happens, your personal information may be disclosed to another company, but that disclosure will be subject to the Privacy Notice in effect.

**f) We may share non-personal information** (such as the number of daily visitors to a particular web page, or the size of an order placed on a certain date) with third parties such as advertising partners. This information does not directly personally identify you or any user.

### UPDATES TO THIS POLICY

If we change or update this Privacy Notice, we will post changes and updates on this Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use, and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Notice from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Notice has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about the Privacy Notice, please contact us.

You can find all contact details at the "Contact us" page or you can leave us a message.

**Fill in the following informations ******
